Why
[laughter]
hey why it's okay hey
tell me it's okay come on why it's okay
Anarkali no [laughter]
wait if you make a
mistake today then I will tell you once I will be wrong so do
n't make a mistake yes if you don't understand then
kill me right now go and do your work
[music]
Ba is the same right isn't
Ba is the same
hey is it the same
Nanu the money is the same right isn't it Nanu the
money is the same yes what are you
son
[music] what am
I doing son [screaming voice]
I am
Reva
[screaming voice]
so I invested the money in Kunda and got
scared Neja go are you ready
yes take it son take it you will get the
reward son your daughter's luck
one trust in the top listen daughter take the clothes I have bought the clothes I have
bought the clothes
[music]
oh
yes dada
oh the lights are on I am
fine go
[music] [
music]
[music]
Dana
see
mistry then call
[music]
hello hello yes hello
Mistry saheb has come out of the house
yes I have heard it from my ears
I am here
Kidna Sharma
yes then brother will fix it yes it's an
hour late Lagastari sahab 50 look hey you
can't fix the light Basti
re re re re Dada is threatening 50 for the
night so now
if you make a mistake yes hey are you
threatening or
threatening tell me the
time yes then tell me it will take half an hour yes then
hurry up yes yes
okay let's go yes all that
quickly Mistry looks Mistry hands empty
Mistry looks there is nothing else
[Music]
said it's Bhabhi's Bhaiya Mistry these days
brother is rich so you make a fuss and did
n't even wake me up after playing a trick that
said Bhabhi it's work a lot the whole day I didn't feel it once I do
n't know let's see when I feel it
just get up and talk just two times it feels yes it feels so fun Khushi Gup
Bhabhi
Khushi Gup is
written here MD Najrul Alam Linem is there a
job Bhabhi
there
electricity department
yes leave it friend you have office Pa Mistry so do the office
work then I will do the work
Bhabhi if I get jealous of tension
Bhabhi
yes do my work mother what is your work brother do
n't forget my marriage [Music] work
mother devotee  So he said if you want to get married then he said
then get married [Music] wait for five years
if it's not right then marry another person for five
years six years if you go then I am
wrong I am beautiful I will forget myself
[Music]
Okay brother when it's like this then I should go to
Dadi Bhabhi Okay
wait brother send me away
yes brother [screaming voice] Okay uncle
[Music]
Okay sister in law I will go
brother will kill you
Okay
[Music]
Noor wait
quickly I
lie down and go and
spend Bansi's money
if you
go [screaming voice] let's go to the doctor
hmm hey you are going to get married right now the
marriage
mason said
oh then
Fana's child then I should get
married today I will get the
work done,
Jai
[Music]
[Music] don't
say anyone by name from the car,
name's name
yes go let the
child come brother come my friend the
child
is born
[Laughter]
son ​​get treatment, get
treatment done, do
n't spoil the fun oh I am better than the doctor, there is
no peace with the doctor only when he eats there is no peace with him
Tillanu
no no re [screaming voice]
Hey, get your lips
fixed, get a mechanic to do the caravan
number. I will give you the breath myself or get you some
rest, instead of torturing you, yes, yes,
son, get the real one. Go get a mechanic to do the
rest.
[Song voice]
Daughter, the medicine is good, the
medicine is good. I
told you, it's good, it's
not good, daughter, daughter, it's good, daughter, aunt,
you just spend 500 rupees,
spend it,
daughter, but the money will be paid, then get the treatment done, then
waste it, daughter,
some call for food,
hey, another
Aslam,
Aslam, hey, here, the
government
line mechanic number, number six, I haven't got the light
fixed, so call me myself,
then Anrik,
yes, brother, Anrik, get the doctor checked, it's
not good, then do
n't worry, take the number,
tell Didi yourself, that's that
[Music] Yes, hello, hello,
hey, I am Aslam Bhaiya,
oh, salam, Walekum, Bhaiya,
Walekum, Salam,
say, sir, that's the whole
matter,
hey, work here  Do the
work, yes
oh light it will take
half an hour, double the time, yes yes
bhaiya let's go and get it cut
[music]
yes ok ok it is
very good yes
thing go
[screaming sound]
another pomegranate is good, get
another treatment done today, just
listen to it, you
say that much in your courtyard, the part is barking, the bastard, is there
anything good
[music]
where is he bhaiya, is he the
mechanic, tell me,
yes, is there a
problem with the light itself
[music]
yes hello hello yes hello hello
yes say say hello
[laughter] yes hello hello oh my, have you
not said hello hello
[laughter]
hey mistri saheb, lie down, turn on the
lighter, saffron for five minutes,
five minutes, I have to
bear it for five minutes, no, no, I am
lying down, I will do
one elephant,
how long will I remove it bhaiya [laughter]
so
move it quickly bhaiya dada take the heat,
yes ok keep it [laughter]
put one strand on yourself, give a strand
[music] the
strand is cut, the
strand is cut,
yes tie it,
good  tie it up
la la
[song voice]
yes come on let's get the
money in hand
[music]
okay yes
okay
[music]
[laughs]
Bhabhi yes Mistry Bhaiya
where is the girl now go and get it done
slow-tempered and very kind-hearted she looks very nice okay do it okay no
problem I don't worry about going there
okay anyway get a job then papers yes yes yes okay
Mistry Bhaiya go
I will inform you then no yes
okay
Bhabhi what is the work call me tell me your
son tell me call me
Suleman sir you get me
married Anarkali I will get a boy married
sir Anarkali is the only boy I have been thinking of getting married the only
boy Mistry I
like to get married I want to get married when I
talk like this then I will
[music]
then I could have got him married then I will have got him
married
hey I know once ok till now
where have I seen a doctor ok ok
brother
this boy should get married
brother he is married he should get
married now tell me what happened
[music]
oh Bhabhi what happened  If
you know me, you should tell me something.
[Music] It's good to try.
Anyway, the
jail of bill roll
means get rid of the bomb. You
got a very good opportunity, otherwise you will regret it for the rest of your life. Pay the
electricity bill, office job,
paper bill, you will regret it for the rest of your life. I went to
tell the boy, who likes you?
I will do it.
Yes brother,
good brother, it's
okay.
[Music]
Meenu,
Meenu, I'm going from
here. Keep sleeping brother,
if you eat, then come here. I'll take
possession of you.
My brother, I'll take possession.
How will I take
possession of you? [Music] [Music] Where have the people gone, Anarkali's feet? [Music] I'm going, I'm going to take possession of you.
Who is the master of the house? [Music]
Look, it's a bill, don't
joke, Babu, don't
joke. Anarkali's
brain is sold, the crazy girl is
selling her brain. Jhalmari says, [Laughs]
I've sold my brain. Jhalmari, why don't you
change your clothes, crazy girl? Then the
girl is there,
who is the boy?  Let's joke, we wo
n't joke
Mistry,
oh
well then [screaming sound]
[laughter]
see
Kanhaiya
[laughter]
[music]
Kanhaiya [music] do it again and again, fly,
yes do it, Oofy [laughter]
yes your walk is improved and clean
[music]
yes Kaniya, how clean she is, may
Allah show her that day [music] then do it
[music]
yes, clean and neat, I will give you
medicine, I have
water,
but not a motorcycle,
I will not keep it there,
yes
[music]
take
Anarkali,
I am
Anarkali
[screaming sound] [music
]
[music]
Assalam Walekum, Namaskar, Aadab.   Till here
if you watch the video then like, share the video
and subscribe to the channel and if this video has
many parts then if you comment well then we
want part two and if we want part three then
you should comment and become a part by the way the
story is very good story,
you have seen it till the end and definitely subscribe ok
now our names, we want to become a channel member so you
listen carefully the first name is MD Arman
Bhai so MD Arman Bhai here photo photo press guys
and channel ID press guys so bh Arman Bhai so
thank you very much become a channel member
second name is Zafar Ali Zafar Ali Bhai so
thank you very much brother var channel ID and
name dakhawa sir thank you very much become a channel
member thank you
Samam Blogs Samam Blogs that channel ID and
channel dakhawa sir thank you very much
become a channel member thank you very much so Tanveer
Alam Bhai Tanveer Alam Bhai Tanveer Alam Bhai so
thank you very much channel member channel
ID and photo
and Sujit Das Bhai Sujit Das Bhai so
thank you very much brother channel member and
Sujit Das Bhai here channel ID and photo guys
thank you very much so
MD  Muntaqim Alam Bhai MD Muntaqim Alam
Bhai so thank you very much become a channel member
and support yourself thank you very much
brother channel ID and photo
[sound of clearing throat] NR's Noor
Jamal Bhai name and channel ID NR's Noor
Jamal Bhai so thank you very much become a channel
member keep supporting thank you very much
support and if you are not a channel member then you can do it
happily,
we will not force you if you want to get support, if you
want to become a channel member then become a channel member by
clicking the join button and some minimum
friends should support the rest if you are not one then they should
support and if you become then they can support
and thank you very much you viewers
video all thank you thank you all
very grateful we salute walekum video
like share subscribe